perdue.com 2015-06-07

# Privacy Policy PERDUE: Chicken & Turkey Recipes, Tips and More

_Effective October 2013_  

_Perdue Salisbury Corporate Office_

_Salisbury, Maryland, United States of America_

Perdue Farms Inc., ("Perdue" or "we") has developed this policy statement (the "Privacy Policy") to assist end users of the Perdue family of Web sites or online social media pages ("you" or "user") in understanding the personally identifiable information gathering and dissemination practices for Perdue's United States Web sites or Perdue's branded and authorized online social media pages, such as Perdue's pages found on FACEBOOK, LINKEDIN, YOUTUBE, TWITTER, or PINTEREST (collectively, the "Site(s)").  Personally identifiable information ("PII") includes information that can be linked to a specific individual, such as a name, address, phone number, or email address. Perdue may modify this Privacy Policy from time to time.  If Perdue makes changes to this Privacy Policy, Perdue will post those changes at this location and provide notice of any material changes so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.  Please review this Privacy Policy on a periodic basis.

**What Information Does Perdue Collect?**

The type of PII collected by Perdue will vary with your use of the Site(s). Perdue gathers most information during the registration processes Perdue utilizes to allow access to and/or use of certain information.  But, Perdue may collect PII at other times, including, but not limited to, when you report a problem with our Site(s), when you complete survey forms, when you access the Career area, enter into a transaction through the Site(s), respond to requests for information or content, and when you request to receive communications from Perdue.  Below, we provide specific examples of the types of PII Perdue may collect through the Site(s).

**Contact Information:** Perdue may request or require contact information, such as your name, address, phone number, facsimile number, and email address.

**Demographic Information:** Perdue may collect demographic and profile data at our Site(s) as a part of its surveys, resume collection features, recipe offerings, advertisements for its products, and/or for management and monitoring purposes in order to continue to improve the Site(s) and the quality of Perdue's on-line services.

**Technical Information:**  Perdue may collect Internet Protocol (IP) addresses from all users of our Site(s) as well as the date and time of access and the Web page(s) accessed. Perdue may also catalog your log-in information and your computer, browser, or operating system information and may maintain a database of aggregated information about the transactions on the Site(s) ( _e.g_., tool or feature utilization or recipe selection data).

**How Does Perdue Use that Information?**

Most of the Site(s) is informational in nature and publicly available to all users. Consequently, until you participate in surveys or register for information from Perdue, you are able to browse the Site(s) without providing any PII, although your browser may tell us what type of computer and operating system you are using as well as other kinds of technical information. Below, is more detail on how Perdue uses your PII.

**Contact Information:** Perdue may use your name and city and state address for testimonials or your contact information for many purposes, including, to advertise its services and the goods and services of third parties, to create a personalized experience for you, to provide you with news and information, to contact you regarding a survey, and to get in touch with you when necessary with respect to transactions conducted through the Site(s), material changes in our Site(s)'s policies and agreements, new services Perdue may offer, or otherwise. We may also share your contact information with our affiliates and business partners, as is necessary to provide our services and information, to facilitate the collection and use of resumes provided through the Site(s)'s "CAREER" area, for advertising purposes, and for internal business purposes. Except for sharing arrangements with Perdue's affiliates, vendors, and business partners, however, we do not share your individual contact information with other types of third parties for any other purpose, except to a court or governmental agency if required by law.

**Demographic Information:** Perdue may share demographic data on an aggregated basis, which will not identify any particular user, with our business partners, vendors, and affiliates or government regulators and for advertising purposes.

**Survey Results:** Perdue may share survey results collected through the Site(s) with its business partners, vendors, and affiliates and/or the general public, the news media, and with the U.S. Government and state governments, not only for business or marketing purposes or as may be required by law, but also to participate in government programs and initiatives.

**Technical Information:** Perdue may use technical information to help diagnose problems with our servers, analyze the Site(s)'s usage trends, track user movements on the Site(s), and to otherwise manage and monitor our Site(s).

**Business Transactions:** In the event that Perdue goes through a business transaction, such as a merger or acquisition by another company involving the sale of all or a portion of its assets, please note that the PII collected and retained by Perdue may be among the assets transferred. In the event a transaction of this kind occurs that results in the transfer of PII, Perdue will notify you via email and/or place a prominent notice on the Site(s) for 30 days of any such change in ownership or control and the possible changes to this Privacy Policy.

**Legal Action:** Perdue may disclose PII when legally required to do so in accordance with government requests or regulations or legal proceedings. We may also disclose PII to protect against misuse or unauthorized use of the Site(s) or as is otherwise required to limit legal liability, protect or defend our rights, property, or interests, or protect the safety, rights, or property of our users.

**What About the Use of Cookies?**

Perdue may use cookies to enhance your experience while using our Site(s). Cookies are pieces of information that Perdue uses for record-keeping purposes, which the Site(s) transfers to your computer's Web-browser for storage on your computer's hard drive. Cookies enable Perdue to customize your experience on the Site(s). Cookies also make Web-surfing easier by automatically performing certain functions such as saving your personal preferences and by ensuring that you do not see the same advertisement repeatedly. Many consider the use of cookies to be an industry standard. Consequently, your Web browser is likely set to accept cookies. If you would prefer not to receive cookies, however, you can alter the configuration of your browser to refuse or delete cookies. If you choose to have your browser refuse or delete cookies, you should understand that it is possible that some areas of our Site(s) will not function properly when you view them.

**What About External or Third Party Web Sites?**

To the extent hyperlinks or gateways (whether through banner advertisements or otherwise) are utilized to access external or third party sites or social media pages, you should be aware that these external or third party sites or pages may collect PII and are not controlled by Perdue and therefore, are not subject to this Privacy Policy. Perdue suggests that you check the privacy policies of these sites or pages to determine how the proprietors of these third party sites will utilize your PII.

**What About Security?**

As is appropriate for the nature of PII collected and stored by Perdue, the Site(s) has industry standard security measures or safeguards in place to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under Perdue's control. Although Perdue has endeavored to create a secure and reliable Site(s), however, the confidentiality of any communication or material cannot be guaranteed. Accordingly, you should consider carefully if you want to submit sensitive information to Perdue. Perdue urges you to take every precaution to protect your PII when on-line.

**What About "Opting-Out" of Data Collection and Use?**

As you are permitted to browse the Site(s) without registering, you can decide on your own if you wish to provide your PII to Perdue (when requested) or opt-out of doing so. For example, if Perdue conducts a survey, you do not have to participate unless you agree to do so. Perdue also provides you with the opportunity to opt-out of certain Perdue business practices where your PII may be used. For example, users may opt-out of having Perdue use your PII in connection with the following activities: (i) inclusion in mailings or (ii) email communications or newsletters sent by Perdue. 

**What About Correcting, Deleting, or Updating Information?**

Perdue will retain your PII for as long as necessary to fulfill the purpose(s) for which it was collected and to comply with applicable laws.  At any time, you may contact Perdue to correct, modify, or delete the information you provide to Perdue through the Site(s). Please note, however, that the collection and uses of certain PII is necessary to provide certain information and services through the Site(s) and the deletion of such necessary information, _e.g._ , an email address, may render a particular service or Perdue's ability to provide it inoperable.

**What About Children?**

Perdue cares about the safety of children on its Site(s) and encourages parents and guardians to monitor their children's use of the Internet. Although the Site(s) is suitable for a general audience, the Site(s) is intended for use only by users who are over 18 years of age or the legal age of majority. Accordingly, Perdue does not knowingly solicit PII from children or send them requests for personal information.

**What About Any Other Questions?**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the information collection and dissemination practices of the Site(s), or Perdue's use of your PII, you can contact Perdue and its employee(s) responsible for its Privacy Policy and related privacy compliance matters by email at [consumerinfopf@cybercrs.net](mailto:consumerinfopf@cybercrs.net), by phone at 1-800-4PERDUE (473-7383), or by mail at Perdue, Salisbury Corporate Office, Attn. Legal Matters, P. O. Box 1537, Salisbury, MD 21802.
